//quiz questions
let questions = [{
    'question': 'How many nations were involved with building the ISS?',
    'correct': '16',
    'a': '12',
    'b': '16'
},
{
    'question': 'The ISS orbits Earth every....?',
    'correct': '90mins',
    'a': '70mins',
    'b': '90mins'
},
{
    'question': 'How many bathrooms are on the ISS?',
    'correct': '2',
    'a': '2',
    'b': '3'
},
{
    'question': 'What was the estimated cost of building the ISS?',
    'correct': '120 Billion',
    'a': '85 Billion',
    'b': '120 Billion'
},
{
    'question': 'Who has spent the most time living in space?',
    'correct': 'Peggy Whitson',
    'a': 'Peggy Whitson',
    'b': 'Chris Hadfield'
},
{
    'question': 'The most days spent living in space?',
    'correct': '665 days',
    'a': '420 days',
    'b': '665 days'
},
{
    'question': 'How many sunsets per day are seen from the ISS?',
    'correct': '16',
    'a': '12',
    'b': '16'
},
{
    'question': 'Number of craft that can connect to the ISS?',
    'correct': '8',
    'a': '5',
    'b': '8'
},
{
    'question': 'In what year did the ISS launch?',
    'correct': '1998',
    'a': '1998',
    'b': '2001'
},
{
    'question': 'Which country is banned from visiting the ISS?',
    'correct': 'China',
    'a': 'China',
    'b': 'Russia'
},
{
    'question': 'Total weight of the ISS in Kgs is?',
    'correct': '419725',
    'a': '379495',
    'b': '419725'
},
{
    'question': 'The ISS has been continuously occupied since? ',
    'correct': 'Nov 2000',
    'a': 'Oct 1999',
    'b': 'Nov 2000'
},
{
    'question': 'How long is the ISS?',
    'correct': '109 metres',
    'a': '109 metres',
    'b': '122 metres'
},
{
    'question': 'Total lines of code written to run the ISS?',
    'correct': '4.5 million',
    'a': '4.5 million',
    'b': '6.5 million'
},
{
    'question': 'How many miles of electrical cable are installed?',
    'correct': '8',
    'a': '6',
    'b': '8'
},
{
    'question': 'How many tourists have visited the ISS?',
    'correct': '7',
    'a': '0',
    'b': '7'
},
{
    'question': 'Strangest thing ever delivered to the ISS?',
    'correct': 'Pizza',
    'a': 'Pizza',
    'b': 'Vodka'
},
{
    'question': 'Journey time from Earth to the ISS is?',
    'correct': '4 Hours',
    'a': '4 Hours',
    'b': '8 Hours'
},
{
    'question': 'How many computers control the systems aboard?',
    'correct': '50',
    'a': '30',
    'b': '50'
},
{
    'question': 'Power is provided by how many solar arrays?',
    'correct': '8',
    'a': '8',
    'b': '10'
}
];

const reloadQuestions = [...questions];